Oluwaseyi Kayode

Nigeria



kayodeoluwaseyi70@gmail.com



07069789179



linkedin.com/in/kayode-oluwaseyi

Summary

I have a Bachelor's degree in Statistics and a diploma certificate in Full-Stack web development. I am an Experienced Technical Support Specialist with a demonstrated history and an enthusiastic serviceoriented personnel with exceptional communication and multitasking abilities.

I also posses the notable skills in proficient manual QA testing.

My resourcefulness and flexibility has helped me blend well since i consistently look out for ways to improve in all areas and put a valuable amount of time in getting better in ways that contribute to my work ethics and environment while gaining an insightful amount of experience as a team player.

Experience



Full-stack Developer

GOMYCODE

Jan 2023 - Present (3 months)



Tech Support Engineer (Tier 2)

Tek Experts

Dec 2021 - Jan 2023 (1 year 2 months)

- Communicate with end users/system administrators of Microsoft Office 365 via phone, email, and/or chat to identify, diagnose, and troubleshoot their needs
- -Apply technical knowledge relevant to the solution using technical documentation to identify appropriate remediation steps, identify escalated urgent situations impacting business priorities.
- -Support Admins In over 10 countries in trouble-shooting cloud based softwares and Escalate complex or atypical cases to higher-level technical support as needed.

Tech support Specialist

Shopify

Jan 2021 - Nov 2021 (11 months)

Sobooster is a remote SaaS tech company that builds apps for Shopify and Big-commerce merchants.

- Interacting with the Shopify merchants using our app and helping them set up the app.
- solve problems relating to the app or answering questions about the app and explaining to the merchants how to use our app features.

-Helping a customer set up the filters on their store or using HTML/CSS/JS to troubleshoot or customize the collection and search pages of the store.

QA Automation Engineer

Justweb

Jan 2020 - Dec 2020 (1 year)

- Design automated end to end tests to check the functionality of web and mobile enterprise applications.
- Write scripts, installs testing protocols, and provides effective test automation solutions, using various testing tools like Selenoid and JUnit.
- Collaborate effectively with a remote team spread across different countries, including creating mutual support groups for new batches of employees

Customer Support Representative

cubeclick Limited

Nov 2018 - Dec 2019 (1 year 2 months)

Education



GOMYCODE

Full-stack JavaScript boot-camp

May 2021 - Oct 2021

Implementation of Full-Stack web development in creating and deploying web apps using the MERN stack



University of Ilorin

Bachelor of Science - BS, Statistics Oct 2015 - Oct 2019

Licenses & Certifications





Full-stack web development - GOMYCODE

Skills

Api • MERN Stack • Troubleshooting • Office 365 • SASS • Office 365 Administration • Microsoft Office • Full-Stack Development • Technical Support • Web Development